HOANG MINH THANH

Data Engineer

♦ hmthanh.github.io → +849 1347 2506 hmthanhgm@gmail.com github.com/hmthanh

Summary: I'm +1^{year} experienced python web developer, have solid background knowledge about Programming Algorithm and Data Structure in University of Science. Proficient Python, C++, experienced in C#, Java and good coding style. I defended my thesis with 9.5 result and ranked excellent. I would like opportunity to work, self-improvement in your company.

EDUCATION

University of Science, VNU-HCM

Sep. 2012 - Sep. 2015

College in Information Technology

University of Science, VNU-HCM

Nov. 2018 - Oct. 2020

Bachelor in Computer Science (GPA: 8.2/10)
Thesis: <u>Link Prediction in Knowledge Graph</u> (9.5/10)

SKILLS

1. KNOWLEDGE & CONCEPT

- Background: Solid Data structure and Algorithm, OOP, Design Pattern (Observer, Factory,..)
- English: Intermediate written and spoken English
- Code versioning tools : Proficient in Git, Github, Gitlab
- Machine Learning; Deep Learning: Attention mechanism, Capsule Neural Network, Knowledge Graph, regularly to reading academic paper.
- Cloud: A bit experience of AWS (S3, EC2, RDS, Route53, Elastic Beanstalk & AWS Seager)
- Parallel programming on GPU: A bit experience of CUDA (kernel, stream, scan, hist)
- Other: WordPress, Heroku, Linux

2. Language & Framework

- C/C++: Data Structures, Class Template, pointer, References, OpenCV 4
- Python: Proficient (PEP 8, lambda, threading pool, ..., numpy, pandas, matplotlib)
- ReactJS: Component Lifecycle, Redux, redux-thunk, redux-saga, React Router, React Hooks
- IDE & Tool: IntelliJ, VS Code (ESLint, Prettier), VIM, sublime
- Database: Good Experience with MS SQL, MySQL, Neo4j
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX, jQuery
- Experience in Django, Flask, ASP.NET MVC, NodeJS

WORK EXPERIENCES AND PROJECT

University of Science VNU - HCM (College)

Sep. 2012 - Sep. 2015

- <u>BietDoiSieuLapLanh</u>: Redesign and customize a template website. I make it even before learn how to code
- Caro Terminator (Self-study) : Basic Al game base on Min-max algorithm on Window Phone using WPF, XAML
- ThuXinh: PHP website of final project
- Pucca Runner (Self-study): A Unity game with funny idea of Dijkstra Algorithm (Play here)

XEP Company (ASP.NET Developer)

2018 - 2019

- Create, customize implement and optimize SQL Query base on requirement
- Develop absolute both front-end and back-end a ecommerce website
- Investigate library to implement image processing of QR code image

Rakumo Co., Ltd (Python Developer)

2019 - 2020

- Maintain Django Website using **Docusign** for Japanese Customer
- Working with team to developing new feature, analyze requirements, estimate implementation, investigate new technology and apply to product.

University of Science VNU – HCM (Bachelor)

Nov. 2018 - Oct. 2020

- Training a LSTM model for handwriting recognition on Colab and deploy to web with TensorflowJS (Draw here).
- <u>Thesis</u>: Modify KBGAT model in Knowledge Graph using Pytorch to create new model named GCAT.

THONORS & AWARDS

• Incentive Award in The Good Chemistry District Student Contest

2009

• Second Round Thach Thuc, Faculty of Information Technology, HCMUS

2013; 2014

CERTIFICATIONS

• Support Student Examination Certification

Aug 2014 - Oct. 2014

Oct. 2014

<u>Critical Thinking</u> (Soft skill)Summer Course Machine Learning

Jun. 2019

• Emotion Recognition Certification - HCMUS

Nov. 2019

• Coursera: Machine Learning

2020

• Golden levelC++, Problem Solving, Bronze levelPython in (3) HackerRank